(Raj:)What is your mother going to say?
She's not gonna see it.
(Howard:)She takes my temperature orally now.
What are you gonna get?
(Howard:)Well, I can't really decide
between a screaming devil...
(Howard:)...this mean little skull,
or Kermit the Frog.
(Bethany:)-Kermit the Frog?
-You know:
[MIMICS KERMIT THE FROG]
"Heigh-ho, I'm on Howard's butt."
[HOWARD CHUCKLES]
(Bethany:)Get the mean little skull,
and I'll see if I can make him smile.
(Howard:)Yeah, I'd like the mean little skull, please.
What are you gonna get, Raj?
(Raj:)With my luck, hepatitis.
(Tattooist:)Okay, here we go.
(Howard:)Ow, ow, ow.
(Tattooist:)That's just rubbing alcohol.
(Howard:)I know, but it was cold.
(Howard:)Ow, ow, ow.
(Tattooist:)I'm putting on the stencil.
(Howard:)-What comes after the stencil?
-This:
[NEEDLE BUZZING]
[SCREAMS]
Aah! Okay, that's it. No needle.
No pain. No tattoo.